ILGWU 4x5 Negatives of Photographs 5780 P N45
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series Price Settlement
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 270)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 271)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 272)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 273)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 274)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 275)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 276)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 277)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 278)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 279)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 280)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 281)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 282)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 283)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 284)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 285)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 286)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 287)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 288)
  - Price Settlement with Century Knit on 147 West 35th Street, 3/24/50, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 289)
  - Press Agreement with Mayor, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 290)
  - Price Settlement Story, 2/56, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 291)
  - Impartial Chairman office Dress Industry, 3/17/54, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 292)
  - Local 60 Price Settlement (Box 23, Folder 293)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 294)
  - Unknown (Box 23, Folder 295)
  - Price Settlement Bureau, 8/54, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 296)
- Series Puerto Rico
  - Puerto Rico Justicia 10/59, 3/160, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Local 142 Spanish meeting, 09/30/53, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Labor Advisory Committee On Puerto Rican affairs, 5/8/54, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Puerto Rico, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Local 66 Puerto Rico, Letter Writing 1/30/66, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Justice, Negotiating Puerto Rican Pact (Brassiere Workers) 1/ 15/56, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - ILGWU Housing Project in Puerto Rico, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Puerto Rican Editor of Spanish Justice distribution at subways on min wage issue. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Meeting for Puerto Rican workers at Roosevelt Hall, David Dubinsky, Hopolito Marcano, 7/14/55, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Series Exhibits: Arts and Crafts
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, 6/2/54, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Art Craft Exhibit at Epiphany Branch Library Local 3 Teachers, 1/14 to 26/52, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Education Deptartment Art Exhibit at ILG 1710 Broadway, 4/22/57, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Arts and Crafts night Spanish speaking get certificate from chairladyship, 5/12/58, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Local 62 Handicraft class, 3/2/53, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Arts and Crafts Exhibit Local 32 May 7 group, Local 132, Local 60, 5/5/58, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Series Chess
  - Recreational Chess, Fall River (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Chess (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Chess (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Retirees Chess game, March 1959 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Series Ceramics
  - Recreational Local 38, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Educational Department Handicrafts (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Recreational Ceramics, 9/13/54, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Local 38 Recreational, Ceramic Class Artworks, 3/4/52, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - ILG Ceramics Class at 60 Headquarters Instructor Pearl Entel, 10/29/51, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Ceramics (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Arts and Craft at 110 E. 16th Street, 10/6/59, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Series Chorus
  - Local 91 Chorus singing at training institution graduation class of 1952, 4/30/52 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Newark, New Jersey Chorus on WFDR, 7/19/51 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Singing around piano (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Northeast Springfield, Mass Chorus conference, 5/25-27/51, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Cloak out of town Department Chorus, 2 Prize Winner, 7/26/50, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Educational Department Singing group, 4/51, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Newark Chorus conductor Ben Wolf, 10/7/50, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Club 22 Member Octavia Morris, 6/22/50, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Chorus (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Radio Passaic Patterson Chorus in Passaic, New Jersey with conductor Ben Wolf, 10/31/51, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Local 60A Chorus (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Local 91 Chorus, 6/54, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Local 91 Chorus integrated, 12/18/54, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 68)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 69)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 70)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 71)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 73)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 74)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 76)
- Series Dancing
  - Local 102 dance (Box 24, Folder 77)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 78)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 79)
  - Duboise Folk Dance at Local 62 offices of Education, 12/8/50, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 80)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 81)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 82)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 83)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 84)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 85)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 86)
  - Dancing (Box 24, Folder 87)
  - Dancing (Box 24, Folder 88)
  - Local 22 Spanish Dance, 4/20/88, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 89)
  - Social Dancing beginners (Box 24, Folder 90)
  - Local 25 Dance class, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 91)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 92)
  - Acrobatics (Box 24, Folder 93)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 94)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 95)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 96)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 97)
  - Local 62 Folk dancing (Box 24, Folder 98)
  - Folk dancing (Box 24, Folder 99)
  - Local 22 children dancing Spanish (Box 24, Folder 100)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 101)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 102)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 103)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 104)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 105)
  - Song Fest (Box 24, Folder 106)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 107)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 108)
  - In-service training, Educational Directors learning to Square dance, 3/18/53, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 109)
  - Special dancing class at ILG, 12/11/53, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 110)
  - Dance conga, 2/56, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 111)
  - Cha-cha dance, 4/30/57, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 112)
  - Local 99 dance class, 5/12/58, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 113)
  - 105 Dance class, 5/58, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 114)
  - Dancing, sculpture and arts and crafts class, 8/6/59, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 115)
  - Dance class Joe Sharky instructor in cha-cha, 1/29/59, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 116)
  - Dance class at Charles Hughes(?) High School 351 West 18th Street, 10/6/59, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 117)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 118)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 119)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 120)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 121)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 122)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 123)
- Series Drawing Painting
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 124)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 125)
  - Art Fall River (Box 24, Folder 126)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 127)
  - Art Class (Box 24, Folder 128)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 129)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 130)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 131)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 132)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 133)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 134)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 135)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 136)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 137)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 138)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 139)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 140)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 141)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 142)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 143)
  - Painting art class (Box 24, Folder 144)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 145)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 146)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 147)
- Series Sculpture
  - Sculpture Class, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 148)
  - Sculpture class 1959Local 62 member Antonio Medina Feliciano at Sofos studio, Employed at Pritty Kiddie Co. 505 Brooklyn, 1/28/59 (Box 24, Folder 149)
  - Retiree does sculpture, bust of Dr. Albert Swertzer, 4/18/55, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 150)
  - Sculpture class Local 22 member Gertrude Gayles, 7/8/52, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 151)
  - Sculpture class, 10/54, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 152)
  - Sculpture class, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 153)
  - Sculpture class (Box 24, Folder 154)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 155)
  - Sculpture class (Box 24, Folder 156)
  - Sculpture, 12/6/51, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 157)
  - Sculpture Class, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 158)
  - Sculpture class, 5/59, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 159)
  - Drawing Class Sofo Studio, 12/55, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 160)
  - Sofo, 1/25/51, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 161)
  - Students at work in April 15 issue of Justice, 4/15/54, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 162)
  - ILGWU Sculpture March 24, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 163)
- Series Theater and Stage
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 164)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 165)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 166)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 167)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 168)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 169)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 170)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 171)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 172)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 173)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 174)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 175)
  - Northeast Department Kayser Roth, Strike skit at Unity House (Box 24, Folder 176)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 177)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 178)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 179)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 180)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 181)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 182)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 183)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 184)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 185)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 186)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 187)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 188)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 189)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 190)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 191)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 192)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 193)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 194)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 195)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 196)
  - Fashion Show ILG workers and Dance rehearsal for Show (Box 24, Folder 197)
- Series Gymnastic
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 198)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 199)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 200)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 201)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 202)
  - Local 140? Glamor (Box 24, Folder 203)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 204)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 205)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 206)
  - Know Your Body class Textile High with instructor Christine Newbert, 2/5/57, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 207)
  - Local 22 Gymnastic class (Box 24, Folder 208)
- Series Hand loom weaving class
  - Hand loom and weaving (Box 24, Folder 209)
- Series Leather Craft
  - Art Craft Local 40, Leather (Box 24, Folder 210)
- Series Players Musicians
  - Local 22 Guitar class, 11/25/52, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 211)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 212)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 213)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 214)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 215)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 216)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 217)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 218)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 219)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 220)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 221)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 223)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 224)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 225)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 226)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 227)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 228)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 229)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 230)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 231)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 232)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 233)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 234)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 235)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 236)
  - Fall River (Box 24, Folder 237)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 238)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 239)
  - ILG Orchestra (Box 24, Folder 240)
  - Club 22 Jamboree wind up, Bob Harder cowboy, 6/22/50, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 241)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 242)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 243)
- Series Miscellaneous
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 244)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 245)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 246)
- Series Sports General
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 247)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 248)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 249)
- Series Sports
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 250)
  - Local 99 Badminton (Box 24, Folder 251)
  - Local 99 gym (Box 24, Folder 252)
  - Local 99 shuffle board (Box 24, Folder 253)
  - Local 99 Ping Pong (Box 24, Folder 254)
  - Ping Pong Easton, Pennsylvania (Box 24, Folder 255)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 256)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 257)
  - Ping Pong player (Box 24, Folder 258)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 259)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 260)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 261)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 262)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 263)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 264)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 265)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 266)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 267)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 268)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 269)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 270)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 271)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 272)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 273)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 274)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 275)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 276)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 277)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 278)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 279)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 280)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 281)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 282)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 283)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 284)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 285)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 286)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 287)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 288)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 289)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 290)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 291)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 292)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 293)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 294)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 295)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 296)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 297)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 298)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 299)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 300)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 301)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 302)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 303)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 304)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 305)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 306)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 307)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 308)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 309)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 310)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 311)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 312)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 313)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 314)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 315)
  - Unknown (Box 24, Folder 316)
- Series Baseball
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Baseball (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Jefferson Park 114st and 1st Avenue Bat- Harvey Hefter Institute Cather Charles Grant Local 91, Local 91- 13 and Training Students 0, 7/18/50, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Local 99 R.H. Miller versus Franklin Stores (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Local 99 Franklin Stores employees team win intro Softball championship, 8/17/54, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Local 99 Baseball team, Batter Local 99 and Catcher Local 60A, 5/54, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Series Basketball
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Basketball gals (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 72)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 73)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 74)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 75)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 76)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 77)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 78)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 79)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 80)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 81)
  - Basketball Charles Evans Hughs High School 351 West 18th Street, 10/6/54, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 82)
  - 99 versus Unity, 8/22/59, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 83)
  - Local 99 versus 60A at Textile High School, 3/17/54, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 84)
  - Local 99, 10/55, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 85)
  - Local 99, 12/49, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 86)
  - Unity House versus Local 99, 9/53, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 87)
  - Local 99 Textile High School Grayson Robinson versus Gaytime, cheering section is Grayson Robinson gals, 1/27/53, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 88)
  - Local 99 Basketball team, 6/13/50, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 89)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 90)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 91)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 92)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 93)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 94)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 95)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 96)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 97)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 98)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 99)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 100)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 101)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 102)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 103)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 104)
- Series Bowling
  - Fall River Bowling (Box 25, Folder 105)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 106)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 107)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 108)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 109)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 110)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 111)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 112)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 113)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 114)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 115)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 116)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 117)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 118)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 119)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 120)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 121)
- Series Gymnastics
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 122)
  - Gymnastics Charles Evans Hughs High School 351 West 18 street, 10/6/59, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 123)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 124)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 125)
  - Gymnastics class at Textile High School, 10/51, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 126)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 127)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 128)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 129)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 130)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 131)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 132)
- Series Swimming
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 133)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 134)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 135)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 136)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 137)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 138)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 139)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 140)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 141)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 142)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 143)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 144)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 145)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 146)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 147)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 148)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 149)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 150)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 151)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 152)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 153)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 154)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 155)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 156)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 157)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 158)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 159)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 160)
  - Local 99 Swimming (Box 25, Folder 161)
  - Local 22 Swimming class at Textile High March 17, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 162)
  - Swimming at Charles Evans Hughs High School 351 W. 18 Street, 10/6/59, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 163)
- Series Tennis
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 164)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 165)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 166)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 167)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 168)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 169)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 170)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 171)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 172)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 173)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 174)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 175)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 176)
- Series Research Department
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 177)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 178)
  - Research Department at work with Dr. Loyar Teper and staff, 4/15/53, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 179)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 180)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 181)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 182)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 183)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 184)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 185)
  - Unknown (Box 25, Folder 186)
- Series Retirees General
  - Samy Kaye, Bells Arons lifetime membership car, 2/4/60, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 187)
  - Golden Ring Club luncheon at International restaurant with Dubinsky, 4/59, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 188)
  - Retirement party Max Gayman and Frank Olivo at Hotel New Yorker (Box 25, Folder 189)
- Series Local 9
  - Nathan and Becky Tabachow Cloak finishers and Manager Harry Fisher, 1/13/59, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 190)
  - Local 9 Retires 180 members, 4/11/54, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 191)
- Series Local 10
  - Retirement party, 10/1/54, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 192)
- Series Local 22, 1922
  - C.S. Zimmerman gives $500 to N.A.A.C.P. Thurgood Marshal, Jack Greenbery, Samuel Shepard and Walter Irwin, 11/16/51, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 193)
  - Dress Retirement party, 10/22/54, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 194)
  - Dress Retirement party, 7/30/53, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 195)
  - Leons dad retires Shop Party, 1/4/56, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 196)
- Series Local 25
  - Retirement Shop Party F.I. Leibowitz, 736 retires 2 members Marie Marchesiella and Clara Rich, 11/19/53 (Box 25, Folder 197)
- Series Local 32
  - Retirees gets life membership card Abe Snyder and Anna Good, 1/7/54, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 198)
- Series Local 35
  - 90 year retiree and group, 11/58, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 199)
- Series Local 38
  - Retiree and 38 people, 1/18/56, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 200)
  - Local 38 1st retirement party David Dubinsky, Samuel Klein and Sal Rosenblatt, 10/4/50, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 201)
- Series Local 48
  - Husband and wife retire, June 12, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 202)
- Series Local 60
  - Man and woman pressers retire, 6/24/53, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 203)
- Series Local 62
  - Retirement, 1/12/53, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 204)
- Series Local 89
  - 3 retirees of Calbo Dress, 1/21/60, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 205)
  - Retirement party for Local 89 officers, 1/8/60, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 206)